Harvard University. Official register of Harvard University, 1900-2008: an inventory
Official register of Harvard University, 1900-2008
- Volume LXV, issued 1968
  - 15. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, general announcement, 1968-1969, August 26, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 110)
  - 16. The Divinity School, 1968-1969, August 29, 1968 (HU 75.25 Box 119)
  - 17. Rules relating to College studies, Harvard-Radcliffe, 1968, August 30, 1968 (HU 75.25 Box 119)
  - 18. Courses of instruction, Harvard and Radcliffe, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1968-1969, September 2, 1968 (HU 75.25 Box 119)
  - 19. Courses of instruction, abridged edition, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1968-1969, September 9, 1968 (HU 75.25 Box 120)
  - 20. Courses in medical sciences, 1968-1969, September 16, 1968 (HU 75.25 Box 119)
  - 21. The Graduate School of Design, September 20, 1968 (HU 75.25 Box 119)
  - 24. Department of Social Relations, October 28, 1968 (HU 75.25 Box 119)
  - 25. Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1966-1967, October 31, 1968 (HU 75.25 Box 119)
  - 26. General catalogue issue, 1968-1969, December 30, 1968 (HU 75.25 Box 120)
- Volume LXVI, issued 1969
  Incomplete. Lacks No. 6. John F. Kennedy School of Government, 1969-1970, June 23, 1969.
  - 1. Advanced standing at Harvard College, 1969-1970, April 1, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 121)
  - 2. Harvard Summer School, 1969, February 5, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 122)
  - 3. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1969-1970, April 15, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 121)
  - 4. Information about Radcliffe College for prospective students, 1969-1970, May 19, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 121)
  - 5. Studies in the freshman year, June 17, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 121)
  - 7. Information about Harvard College, June 30, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 121)
  - 8. Rules relating to College studies, Harvard-Radcliffe, 1969, July 16, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 121)
  - 9. Harvard School of Public Health, 1969-1970, July 23, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 121)
  - 10. Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, higher degrees in biology, supplement to the general announcement, July 30, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 121)
  - 11. Scholarship, beneficiary aid and loan funds of Harvard College, 1969, January 22, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 121)
  - 12. Courses of instruction, Harvard and Radcliffe, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1969-1970, August 15, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 121)
  - 13. The Law School, catalogue for 1969-1970, August 19, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 122)
  - 14. The Graduate School of Design, August 22, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 121)
  - 15. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, general announcement, 1969-1970, August 26, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 121)
  - 17. The Divinity School, 1969-1970, August 29, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 121)
  - 18. Graduate School of Education and the Master of Arts in Teaching program, 1969-1970, September 4, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 121)
  - 19. Courses of instruction, abridged edition, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1969-1970, September 12, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 121)
  - 22. Harvard School of Dental Medicine, 1969-1970, September 23, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 121)
  - 23. Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1967-1968, September 30, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 122)
  - 26. General catalogue issue, 1969-1970, December 30, 1969 (HU 75.25 Box 122)
- Volume LXVII, issued 1970
  - 1. Harvard Summer School, 1970, January 30, 1970 (HU 75.25 Box 123)
  - 2. The Law School, catalogue for 1970-1971, limited temporary edition, February 27, 1970 (HU 75.25 Box 123)
  - 3. Studies in the freshman year, April 10, 1970 (HU 75.25 Box 123)
  - 4. Advanced standing at Harvard College, 1970-1971, April 22, 1970 (HU 75.25 Box 124)
  - 5. John Fitzgerald Kennedy School of Government, 1970-1971, May 31, 1970 (HU 75.25 Box 123)
  - 8. Graduate School of Education and the Master of Arts in Teaching program, 1970-1971, June 26, 1970 (HU 75.25 Box 123)
  - 9. Harvard School of Public Health, 1970-1971, July 3, 1970 (HU 75.25 Box 124)
  - 10. Harvard Graduate School of Business Administration, 1970-1971, July 15, 1970 (HU 75.25 Box 123)
  - 12. Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, higher degrees in biology, supplement to the general announcement, August 5, 1970 (HU 75.25 Box 124)
  - 13. Information about Harvard College, August 12, 1970 (HU 75.25 Box 123)
  - 14. Information about Radcliffe College for prospective students, August 19, 1970 (HU 75.25 Box 123)
  - 15. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, general announcement, 1970-1971, August 26, 1970 (HU 75.25 Box 123)
  - 16. The Divinity School, 1970-1971, August 28, 1970 (HU 75.25 Box 123)
  - 17. Courses of instruction for Harvard and Radcliffe, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1970-1971, August 31, 1970 (HU 75.25 Box 123)
  - 18. Rules relating to College studies, Harvard-Radcliffe, 1970, September 3, 1970 (HU 75.25 Box 123)
  - 19. Harvard Law School catalogue, 1970-1971, September 10, 1970 (HU 75.25 Box 123)
  - 21. Catalogue of the Graduate School of Design, 1970-1971, September 18, 1970 (HU 75.25 Box 123)
  - 22. Courses of instruction, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, preliminary and abridged edition, 1970-1971, September 18, 1970 (HU 75.25 Box 124)
  - 23. Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1968-1969, October 30, 1970 (HU 75.25 Box 120)
  - 26. General catalogue issue, 1970-1971, December 30, 1970 (HU 75.25 Box 123)
- Volume LXVIII, issued 1971
  - 1. Harvard Summer School, 1971, January 30, 1971 (HU 75.25 Box 125)
  - 2. Harvard Law School catalog, 1971-1972, February 26, 1971 (HU 75.25 Box 125)
  - 4. Courses of instruction for Harvard and Radcliffe, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1971-1972, April 16, 1971 (HU 75.25 Box 125)
  - 5. Studies in the freshman year, May 28, 1971 (HU 75.25 Box 125)
  - 6. Advanced standing at Harvard College and Radcliffe Collge, 1971-1972, June 15, 1971 (HU 75.25 Box 125)
  - 8. Harvard School of Public Health, 1971-1972, June 28, 1971 (HU 75.25 Box 125)
  - 9. The Divinity School, 1971-1972, July 12, 1971 (HU 75.25 Box 125)
  - 10. Graduate School of Education and the Master of Arts in Teaching program, 1971-1972, July 16, 1971 (HU 75.25 Box 125)
  - 11. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1971-1972, July 30, 1971 (HU 75.25 Box 125)
  - 12. Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of the departments, 1969-1970, August 12, 1971 (HU 75.25 Box 121)
  - 14. John Fitzgerald Kennedy School of Government, 1971-1972, August 19, 1971 (HU 75.25 Box 125)
  - 15. Graduate School of Business Administration, the doctoral program, 1971-1972, August 23,1971 (HU 75.25 Box 125)
  - 16. Information about Harvard College, August 26, 1971 (HU 75.25 Box 125)
  - 17. Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, higher degrees in biology, supplement to the general announcement,August 30, 1971 (HU 75.25 Box 125)
  - 18. Rules relating to College studies, Harvard-Radcliffe, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1971-1972, September 5, 1971 (HU 75.25 Box 125)
  - 19. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, general announcement, 1971-1972, September 10, 1971 (HU 75.25 Box 125)
  - 20. Information about Radcliffe College for prospective students, September 17, 1971 (HU 75.25 Box 125)
  - 21. The Graduate School of Design, 1971-1972, September 24, 1971 (HU 75.25 Box 125)
  - 23. Instruction in oceanography offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1971, October 1, 1971 (HU 75.25 Box 125)
- Volume LXIX, issued 1972
  - 1. Harvard Summer School, 1972, January 31, 1972 (HU 75.25 Box 126)
  - 3. Studies in the freshman year, April 21, 1972 (HU 75.25 Box 126)
  - 4. Courses of instruction for Harvard-Radcliffe, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1972-1973, April 28, 1972 (HU 75.25 Box 126)
  - 5. Harvard School of Public Health, 1972-1973, May 31, 1972 (HU 75.25 Box 125)
  - 6. Advanced standing at Harvard College and Radcliffe College, 1972-1973, June 16, 1972 (HU 75.25 Box 126)
  - 7. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1972-1973, June 23, 1972 (HU 75.25 Box 126)
  - 8. Information about Harvard College, June 30, 1972 (HU 75.25 Box 126)
  - 9. The Graduate School of Design, 1972-1973, July 11, 1972 (HU 75.25 Box 126)
  - 10. Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, higher degrees in biology, supplement to the general announcement, July 18, 1972 (HU 75.25 Box 126)
  - 12. Rules relating to College studies, Harvard-Radcliffe, 1972,August 1, 1972 (HU 75.25 Box 126)
  - 13. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, general announcement, 1973-1973, August 4, 1972 (HU 75.25 Box 126)
  - 14. John Fitzgerald Kennedy School of Government, 1972-1973, August 18, 1972 (HU 75.25 Box 126)
  - 16. The Divinity School, 1972-1973, August 29, 1972 (HU 75.25 Box 126)
  - 17. Information about Radcliffe College for prospective students, August 31, 1972 (HU 75.25 Box 126)
  - 18. Graduate School of Education and the Master of Arts in Teaching program, 1972-1973, September 7, 1972 (HU 75.25 Box 126)
  - 19. Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1970-1971, September 15, 1972 (HU 75.25 Box 123)
- Volume LXX, issued 1973
  - 1. Harvard Summer School, 1973, January 31, 1973 (HU 75.25 Box 127)
  - 2. General catalogue issue, 1973-1974, April 30, 1973 (HU 75.25 Box 126)
  - 3. The Divinity School, 1973-1974, April 20, 1973 (HU 75.25 Box 127)
  - 4. Studies in the freshman year, May 31, 1973 (HU 75.25 Box 127)
  - 5. Advanced standing at Harvard College and Radcliffe College, 1973-1974, June 16, 1973 (HU 75.25 Box 127)
  - 6. Harvard School of Public Health, 1973-1974, June 22, 1973 (HU 75.25 Box 127)
  - 7. Faculty of Arts and Sciences, courses of instruction, 1973-1974, June 29, 1973 (HU 75.25 Box 127)
  - 8. Harvard Graduate School of Design, 1973-1974, July 11, 1973 (HU 75.25 Box 127)
  - 9. Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, higher degrees in biology, supplement to the general announcement, July 31, 1973 (HU 75.25 Box 127)
  - 11. Information about Harvard College, August 10, 1973 (HU 75.25 Box 127)
  - 12. John Fitzgerald Kennedy School of Government, 1973-1974, August 17, 1973 (HU 75.25 Box 127)
  - 13. Rules relating to College studies, Harvard-Radcliffe, 1973-1974, August 24, 1973 (HU 75.25 Box 127)
  - 14. Harvard Law School catalog, 1973-1974, August 31, 1973 (HU 75.25 Box 127)
  - 15. Information about Radcliffe College for prospective students, September 6, 1973 (HU 75.25 Box 127)
  - 17. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, general announcement, 1973-1974, September 20, 1973 (HU 75.25 Box 127)
  - 19. Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1971-1972, November 30, 1973 (HU 75.25 Box 125)
- Volume LXXI, issued 1974
  - 1. Harvard Summer School, 1974, January 31, 1974 (HU 75.25 Box 128)
  - 2. The Divinity School, 1974-1975, April 30, 1974 (HU 75.25 Box 128)
  - 3. Courses of instruction, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1974-1975, April 30, 1974 (HU 75.25 Box 128)
  - 4. Harvard School of Public Health, 1974-1975, May 31, 1974 (HU 75.25 Box 128)
  - 6. Advanced standing at Harvard College and Radcliffe College, 1974-1975, June 26, 1974 (HU 75.25 Box 128)
  - 7. Rules relating to College studies, general academic rules, Harvard and Radcliffe Colleges, 1974-1975, June 18, 1974 (HU 75.25 Box 128)
  - 8. Rules relating to College studies, fields of concentration, Harvard and Radcliffe Colleges, 1974-1975, July 12, 1974 (HU 75.25 Box 128)
  - 9. John Fitzgerald Kennedy School of Government, 1974-1975, July 31, 1974 (HU 75.25 Box 128)
  - 10. Harvard Graduate School of Design, 1974-1975, August 1, 1974 (HU 75.25 Box 128)
  - 11. Harvard Law School catalog, 1974-1975, August 9, 1974 (HU 75.25 Box 128)
  - 12. Information about Harvard College, August 16, 1974 (HU 75.25 Box 128)
  - 13. Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, higher degrees in biology, supplement to the general announcement, August 23, 1974 (HU 75.25 Box 128)
  - 14. General catalogue issue, 1973-1974, August 30, 1974 (HU 75.25 Box 127)
  - 15. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, general announcement, 1974-1975, September 6, 1974 (HU 75.25 Box 128)
  - 18. Information about Radcliffe College for prospective students, 1974-1975, July 20, 1974 (HU 75.25 Box 128)
- Volume LXXII, issued 1975, Note in shelflist: All these are handled by individual dept. now.
  - 1. The Divinity School, 1975-1976, May 2, 1975 (HU 75.25 Box 129)
  - 3. Harvard Graduate School of Design, 1975-1976, July 25, 1975 (HU 75.25 Box 129)
  - 4. Courses of instruction, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1975-1976, August 1, 1975 (HU 75.25 Box 129)
  - 5. Rules relating to College studies, general academic rules, 1975-1976, August 12, 1975 (HU 75.25 Box 129)
  - 6. Rules relating to College studies, fields of concentration, Harvard and Radcliffe Colleges, 1975-1976, August 18, 1975 (HU 75.25 Box 129)
  - 7. Harvard Graduate School of Education, 1975-1976, August 19, 1975 (HU 75.25 Box 129)
  - 8. Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Higher degrees in biology, supplement to the general announcement, August 22, 1975 (HU 75.25 Box 129)
  - 9. Harvard Law School catalog, 1975-1976, August 29, 1975 (HU 75.25 Box 129)
  - 9. Harvard Law School, September 2, 1975 (HU 75.25 Box 129)
  - 11. Information about Harvard and Radcliffe, September 5, 1975 (HU 75.25 Box 129)
  - 12. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, general announcement, 1975-1976, September 10, 1975 (HU 75.25 Box 129)
  - 13. General catalogue issue, 1974-1975, October 30, 1975 (HU 75.25 Box 128)
  - 14. Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of the departments, 1973-1974, November 5, 1975 (HU 75.25 Box 129)
  - John F. Kennedy School of Government, 1975-1976 (HU 75.25 Box 129)
- Volume LXXIII, issued 1976
  - 1. The Divinity School, 1976-1977, June 2, 1976 (HU 75.25 Box 130)
  - 2. Harvard School of Public Health, 1976-1977, July 5, 1976 (HU 75.25 Box 130)
  - 7. Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1974-1975, January 10, 1977 (HU 75.25 Box 130)
  - 12. Information about Harvard and Radcliffe, August 1976 (HU 75.25 Box 130)
  - Courses of instruction, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1976-1977, August 1976 (HU 75.25 Box 130)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, higher degrees in biology, supplement to the general announcement, August 1976 (HU 75.25 Box 130)
  - Rules relating to College studies, Harvard and Radcliffe Colleges, fields of concentration, 1976-1977 (HU 75.25 Box 130)
  - Rules relating to College students, general academic rules, Harvard and Radcliffe Colleges, 1976-1977 (HU 75.25 Box 130)
  - The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, general announcement, 1976-1977, September 1976 (HU 75.25 Box 130)
  - Harvard and Radcliffe, undergraduate regulations and services, 1976-1977 (HU 75.25 Box 130)
  - General catalogue, 1976-1977 (HU 75.25 Box 130)
- Volume LXXIV, issued 1977
  - 1. The Divinity School, 1977-1978, June 10, 1977 (HU 75.25 Box 131)
  - 4. Harvard School of Public Health, 1977-1978, July 15, 1977 (HU 75.25 Box 131)
  - 5. Information about Harvard and Radcliffe, August 1977 (HU 75.25 Box 131)
  - 8. Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1975-1976, October 25, 1977 (HU 75.25 Box 131)
  - The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, general announcement, 1977-1978, September 1977 (HU 75.25 Box 131)
  - Courses of instruction, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1977-1978 (HU 75.25 Box 131)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, higher degrees in biology, supplement to the general announcement, August 1977 (HU 75.25 Box 131)
  - John Fitzgerald Kennedy School of Government, 1977-1978 (HU 75.25 Box 131)
  - Harvard Graduate School of Design, 1977-1978 (HU 75.25 Box 131)
  - Undergraduate regulations and services, Harvard and Radcliffe Colleges, 1977-1978 (HU 75.25 Box 131)
  - Harvard College and Radcliffe College, the freshman seminar program, 1977-1978 (HU 75.25 Box 131)
  - General catalogue, 1977-1978, November 1978 (HU 75.25 Box 131)
  - Fields of concentration, Harvard and Radcliffe Colleges, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1977-1978 (HU 75.25 Box 131)
- Volume LXXV, issued 1978
  Incomplete. Lacks Courses of instruction, 1978-1979 and Report of the President, 1976-1977, August 4, 1978.
  - 6. Information about Harvard and Radcliffe, August 1978 (HU 75.25 Box 132)
  - The Divinity School, 1978-1979, June 2, 1978 (HU 75.25 Box 132)
  - Handbook for students in Harvard and Radcliffe Colleges, 1978-1979 (HU 75.25 Box 132)
  - Fields of concentration, Harvard and Radcliffe Colleges, 1978-1979 (HU 75.25 Box 132)
  - Harvard Graduate School of Design, 1978-1979 (HU 75.25 Box 132)
  - General catalogue, 1978-1979, January 1979 (HU 75.25 Box 132)
  - Harvard School of Public Health, 1978-1979, August 30, 1978 (HU 75.25 Box 132)
- Volume 1, 1979-1980
  Incomplete. Lacks Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1979-1980, July 2, 1981.
  - Vol. 1, no. 1. Harvard Law School, August 25, 1979 (HU 75.25 Box 133)
  - Vol. 1, no. 3. Harvard School of Public Health, 1979-1980, September 10, 1979 (HU 75.25 Box 133)
  - Vol. 1, no. 5. Harvard University Center for Lifelong Learning, spring 1980, December 21, 1979 (HU 75.25 Box 133)
  - Vol. 1, no. 5. Harvard Summer School, 1980, February 29, 1980 (HU 75.25 Box 133)
  - Vol. 1, no. 7. Harvard Graduate School of Design, 1979-1980, September 5, 1979 (HU 75.25 Box 133)
  - Courses of instruction, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1979-1980 (HU 75.25 Box 133)
  - Changes to courses of instruction, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, Fall 1979 (HU 75.25 Box 133)
  - Handbook for students in Harvard and Radcliffe College,1979-1980 (HU 75.25 Box 133)
  - Fields of concentration, Harvard and Radcliffe Colleges, 1979-1980 (HU 75.25 Box 133)
  - General catalogue, 1979-1980, November 1979 (HU 75.25 Box 133)
  - Graduate Schoool of Arts and Sciences, higher degrees in biology, July 1979 (HU 75.25 Box 133)
  - Harvard Graduate School of Education, 1979-1980 (HU 75.25 Box 133)
  - Information about Harvard and Radcliffe, 1979-1980, August 1979 (HU 75.25 Box 133)
- Volume 2, 1980-1981
  - Vol. 2, no. 1. Harvard Divinity School, 1980-1981, July 1, 1980 (HU 75.25 Box 134)
  - Vol. 2, no. 2. Harvard School of Public Health, 1980-1981, July 30, 1980 (HU 75.25 Box 134)
  - Vol. 2, no. 3. Harvard Commission on Extension Courses, 1980-1981, August 15, 1980 (HU 75.25 Box 134)
  - Vol. 2, no. 4. Harvard Law School catalog and application, August 25, 1980 (HU 75.25 Box 134)
  - Vol. 2, no. 5. Harvard Graduate School of Design, 1980-1981, September 5, 1980 (HU 75.25 Box 134)
  - Vol. 2, no. 6. Courses of instruction, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1980-1981, September 10, 1980 (HU 75.25 Box 134)
  - Vol. 2, no. 7. General catalogue, 1980-1981, October 15, 1980 (HU 75.25 Box 134)
  - Vol. 2, no. 8. Harvard Summer School, 1981, February 27, 1981 (HU 75.25 Box 134)
  - John F. Kennedy School of Government, catalogue, 1980-1981 (HU 75.25 Box 134)
  - John F. Kennedy School of Government, courses of instruction, 1980-1981 (HU 75.25 Box 134)
  - Information, Harvard Medical School, Harvard School of Dental School, [1979-1980] (HU 75.25 Box 134)
  - Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1978-1979, July 2, 1980 (HU 75.25 Box 132)
- Volume 3, 1981-1982
  - Vol. 3, no. 1. Harvard Divinity School, 1981-1982, July 1, 1981 (HU 75.25 Box 135)
  - Vol. 3, no. 2. Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, general announcement, 1981-1982, July 31, 1981 (HU 75.25 Box 135)
  - Vol. 3, no. 3. Harvard School of Public Health, 1981-1982,August 1, 1981 (HU 75.25 Box 135)
  - Vol. 3, no. 4. Harvard Extension School catalogue, 1981-1982, August 10, 1981 (HU 75.25 Box 135)
  - Vol. 3, no. 6. Courses of instruction, 1981-1982, September 8, 1981 (HU 75.25 Box 135)
  - Vol. 3, no. 6. Information about Harvard and Radcliffe, 1981-1982, August 20, 1981 (HU 75.25 Box 135)
  - Vol. 3, no. 7. Harvard Graduate School of Design, 1981-1982, September 15, 1981 (HU 75.25 Box 135)
  - Vol. 3, no. 8. Harvard Law School catalog and application, September 1981 (HU 75.25 Box 135)
  - Vol. 3, no. 10. General catalogue, 1981-1982, October 15, 1981 (HU 75.25 Box 135)
  - Vol. 3, no. 11. Harvard Summer School, 1982, February 27, 1982 (HU 75.25 Box 135)
  - Vol. 3, no. 12. Harvard Medical School course catalogue, 1982-1983, March 1, 1982 (HU 75.25 Box 135)
  - Harvard Medical School course catalog, 1981-1982, March 1, 1981 (HU 75.25 Box 135)
    Labelled as Vol. 2, no. 9.
  - John F. Kennedy School of Government, catalogue, 1981-1982 (HU 75.25 Box 135)
  - Harvard Medical School course catalogue supplement 1,1982-1983 (HU 75.25 Box 135)
  - Fields of concentration, 1981-1982 (HU 75.25 Box 135)
- Volume 4, 1982-1983
  - Vol. 4, no. 1, Harvard Divinity School, 1982-1983, July 1, 1982 (HU 75.25 Box 136)
  - Vol. 4, no. 2. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, general announcement, 1982-1983, July 31, 1982 (HU 75.25 Box 136)
  - Vol. 4, no. 4. Harvard School of Public Health, 1982-1983, August 10, 1982 (HU 75.25 Box 136)
  - Vol. 4, no 5. Harvard Extension School catalogue, 1982-1983, April 11, 1982 (HU 75.25 Box 136)
  - Vol. 4, no. 6. Information about Harvard and Radcliffe, 1982-1983, August 1982 (HU 75.25 Box 136)
  - Vol. 4, no. 7. Graduate School of Design,1982-1983, September 1, 1982 (HU 75.25 Box 136)
  - Vol. 4, no. 9. Courses of instruction, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1982-1983, September 8, 1982 (HU 75.25 Box 136)
  - Vol. 4, no. 10. General catalogue, 1982-1983, October 15, 1982 (HU 75.25 Box 136)
  - Vol. 4, no. 11. Harvard Summer School catalogue, 1983, February 27, 1983 (HU 75.25 Box 136)
  - Vol. 4, no. 12. Harvard Medical School course catalog, 1983-1984 (HU 75.25 Box 136)
  - Harvard Medical School course catalog supplement 1, 1983-1984 (HU 75.25 Box 136)
  - John F. Kenendy School of Government catalogue, 1982-1983 (HU 75.25 Box 136)
  - Fields of concentration, Harvard and Radcliffe Colleges, 1982-1983 (HU 75.25 Box 136)
  - Handbook for students, Harvard College, 1982-1983 (HU 75.25 Box 136)
  - Harvard Law School catalogue, 1982-1983 (HU 75.25 Box 136)
  - Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1980-1981, July 2, 1982 (HU 75.25 Box 134)
- Volume 5, 1983-1984
  - Vol. 5, no. 1. Harvard Divinity School, 1983-1984, July 1, 1983 (HU 75.25 Box 137)
  - Vol. 5, no. 2. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, general announcement, 1983-1984, July 2, 1983 (HU 75.25 Box 137)
  - Vol. 5, no. 3. University Extension course catalogue, 1983-1984, July 12, 1983 (HU 75.25 Box 137)
  - Vol. 5, no. 6. Courses of instruction, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1983-1984, August 10, 1983 (HU 75.25 Box 137)
  - Vol. 5, no. 6. Fields of concentration, Harvard and Radcliffe Colleges, 1983-1984, August 10, 1983 (HU 75.25 Box 137)
  - Vol. 5, no. 7. School of Public Health catalogue, 1983-1984, August 17, 1983 (HU 75.25 Box 137)
  - Vol. 5, no. 8. Information about Harvard and Radcliffe, 1983-1984, August 20, 1983 (HU 75.25 Box 137)
  - Vol. 5, no. 9. Graduate School of Design, 1983-1984, September 1, 1983 (HU 75.25 Box 137)
  - Vol. 5, no. 10. Graduate School of Education catalogue, 1983-1984, September 2, 1983 (HU 75.25 Box 137)
  - Vol. 5, no. 11. General catalogue, 1983-1984, November 15, 1982 (HU 75.25 Box 137)
  - Vol. 5, no. 12. Harvard Summer School, 1984, February 27, 1984 (HU 75.25 Box 137)
  - Vol. 5, no. 13. Harvard Medical School, course catalogue, 1984-1985 (HU 75.25 Box 137)
  - Vol. 5, no. 13. University Extension course catalogue, 1984-1985, July 12, 1984 (HU 75.25 Box 137)
  - Harvard Medical School, course catalogue, supplement 1, 1984-1985 (HU 75.25 Box 137)
  - Handbook for students, Harvard College, 1983-1984 (HU 75.25 Box 137)
  - John F. Kennedy School of Government, catalogue, 1983-1984 (HU 75.25 Box 137)
- Volume 6, 1984-1985
  Incomplete. Lacks Summer School, 1984.
  - Vol. 6, no. 1. Harvard Divinity School, 1984-1985, July 1, 1984 (HU 75.25 Box 138)